hey everyone caffeine man here and today
we're going to be going over part two of
my healthier energy drink series what's
this healthier energy drink it's called
Celsius and trust me is healthy it's
like one Awards and stuff so you know
it's got to be good plus if you like
these healthier energy drink videos that
I've been doing leave me comments down
below and I'll continue to bring you a
few more healthier energy drinks but if
not you'll have to find the healthier
energy drinks on your
[Music]
own hello again everyone thank you so
much for joining me today today we are
on to part two of my healthier energy
drink series part one seemed to go okay
and you know I had some comments but it
could have just been the product that I
reviewed so I decided to give it one
more try and this time it's with Celsius
I got a good feeling about this one it's
one Awards there's been studies backing
how good it is plus a few people even
requested me to do a video on it but
once again definitely leave me some
comments down below because if it
doesn't go well moving on to other stuff
also if you want to stay informed on all
things caffeine related hit the
Subscribe button I post new videos every
Tuesday night so first off I'm going to
tell you a little bit about this drink
then I'll give you a little history
about the company Celsius after that I'm
going to go through the ingredients that
make it special and for the grand finale
I have several flavors that I'm going to
try out but not all 14 of them also to
make it easier for you guys to find out
the information you're most interested
in check out the description box down
below I'm going to put a time stamp for
each section that way the people that
want the taste test can go right to the
taste test and the people that want to
know more about the the company can go
about the company let's Jump Right In to
this healthier energy drink and
hopefully they're not too mad that I'm
calling it a healthy energy drink
because they declare themselves as a
fitness drink excuse me could you tell
me where the fitness drink section
is so what makes it a fitness drink
according to their website it's a
thermogenic drink as a thermogenic its
metal plus propriety blend accelerates
metabolism increasing your body's
ability to burn fat and calories they
say there are only two ways that the
body burns fat through increased heart
rate and or increased body temperature
thermogenesis when you drink Celsius and
exercise you're doing both helping
accelerate the burn thus faster results
if you check out the Celsius website
you'll also find six University
published studies that have been done on
Celsius by us accredited scientific
research facilities and honestly I just
repeated that like seven times these
studies all show positive results
reinforcing it as a fitness drink I'm
still calling it an energy drink so a
little bit about the company
in June of 2005 Celsius released its
first three flavors Cola lemon lime and
ginger ale they came in a glass bottle
you know before cans were popular then
in 2007 they released two new flavors
orange and wild berry they also released
two non-carbonated versions yay
raspberry asai and peach mango two of my
favorite flavors in general what else
did they do in 2007 they switched over
to cans because it became popular and
probably cheaper over the next decade
they had a bunch of universities do do
studies on their drinks and they won a
bunch of awards for health taste and
Innovation they also began releasing a
lot more flavors as of 2019 they have 14
different flavors four on the- go powder
versions and seven of the newly released
Celsius heat and Celsius heat it's like
their super workout energy drink Fitness
drink the heat has 300 Mig of caffeine
sounds familiar and 2,000 mg of L
citrine plus a bunch of other stuff but
this review is for Celsius not Celsius
heat so you'll have to wait your turn
Celsius heat so what flavors are there
and what's in this drink for the
originals line six out of the eight are
sparkling beverages that makes two
non-carbonated ones which I'm very
excited to try out they also have six
other flavors that are made with stevia
since the original line uses sucos and
for some reason there's a bunch of
people that go crazy over sucos oh it's
evil so they made some with stevia as
well three of them are sparkling three
of them are not and I don't actually
have any of the stevia wants to try out
just the originals and what the
nutrition tax panel have to say well
it's crazy all over the place it's got
over 100% daily value on a whole bunch
of the stuff and I mean it's just super
healthy with everything that's in it I
mean hey just look at that look at all
those numbers right there I'm going to
put that picture right there and feel
free to pause the video to read all
those numbers I'll
wait so as you can see lots of good
stuff we all know that vitamin C is good
for you and when it comes to Vitamin B
yeah it's good that they're all over
100% but you're probably just going to
pee out anything over the 100% unless
you're deficient and vitamin B but still
good to have especially if you're
working out but besides all that stuff
what makes this extra healthy it's the
metal plus proprietary blend this blend
has a full whopping 1.81 G of this
proprietary blend this blend has green
tea extract in it green tea itself is
the second healthiest drink on the
planet falling short to first place
which is actually water it is full of
antioxidants and egcg's what are EC gc's
egcg's are amazing and if you want to
learn more about them feel free to check
out my tea talk series I did a full
series where I go over all the health
benefits of tea including greed tea and
ecg's for the sake of this video and
fitness drink scientists have proven
that it boosts your metabolism which
allows you to effectively burn more
calories and store less fat it's also
good Ginger extract which is super good
for you plus toine toine has been known
to help with heart health and works as
an antioxidant helping stimulate the
muscles to offer better performance for
athletes it also uses Guana extract
what's Guana EXT ract found in the
Amazon rainforest Guana provides a
natural source of caffeine but unlike
most Guana drinks Celsius uses the seeds
instead of the roots which contain twice
the amount of caffeine as your average
Coffee Bean that stuff that stuff has
been known to Boost energy lessen
sleepiness and increase alertness and
reaction time Studies have also shown
that that stuff positively impacts human
mental performance and mood when used in
combination with torine and caffeine
which Celsius also has toine also does
some other good sciency natural stuff in
your body as well but that's good for
now you know what I like about this
drink you know what I like about this
drink this can has 200 mg of caffeine
that's right this 12 oz can has 200 Mig
how does that compare a normal Red Bull
12 oz can has 114 mg so this is
considerably more how do it compared to
all the other energy drinks given that
there are so many different energy
drinks with different sizes 8 oz 12 oz
16 oz and higher the best way to measure
its caffeine content is by how many
milligrams per ounce no matter what the
size Red Bull and Monster come in at
around 10 mg per ounce bang and Rain
they both come in at about 19 mg per
ounce Celsius comes in Just Around 17 mg
per ounce so you're going to be able to
feel the caffeine because it's very
similar to bang and Rain even though
it's only 200 and they're 300 it's 200
and a 12 oz can as opposed to a 6 18 Oz
can which is why I always measure it by
milligram per ounce now let's taste them
for the sparkling flavors I'm going to
review four of them today and those
include grape Rush orange wild berry and
watermelon for the non-sparkling
versions I'm going to do the raspberry
acai and the peach mango so let's start
off with a sparkling one the grape
brush oh wow that's pretty good I
normally don't don't like sparkling
beverages so I'm trying to put my bias
to the side but you know what this is a
lightly sparkling beverage do they even
say
that I don't even see that on here but
usually companies like to advertise that
they're lightly sparkling and this is
lightly sparkling I can barely taste any
of that sparkling flavor and the grape
it's really good I mean it reminds me of
like a grape juice but keep in mind
these drinks don't have any sugar in
them they use sucrose but they put the
perfect amount of sucrose in here so
that it's not too sweet but it's got a
really great grape flavor I mean I
usually don't like grape but this is
good I'm having some
more not too much I'm having five more
next up is the sparkling
[Music]
orange yeah that one's pretty good too
it didn't hit me like the grape hit me
the grape had a strong grape flavor this
is a little bit of a lighter orange
flavor you definitely get the orange out
of it and it also has that light
sparkling flavor which I wouldn't even
say is a sparkling flavor these aren't
your typical sparkling Beverages and
similar to The Grape it's not too sweet
so the amount of suc that they put in is
pretty low so for all you super low
freaks there's not much in here but it
still tastes good I'm not sure which one
to try next they all look so good next
is the wild
berry H okay that one's pretty good too
once again I'm not going to harp on the
fact that these are lightly sparkling
I'm going to put that to the side so I
have to keep repeating myself they seem
like they're all lightly sparkling so
let's focus on the flavor this Berry
flavor is a light Berry flavor it's got
a hint of raspberry it's got a hint of
blueberry and I think the raspberry is
Just a Little Bit Stronger it's got a
little bit of sweetness to it so far the
strongest flavor has been the grape the
least strongest has been the orange and
this one Falls right in between the two
I mean this is great it's a healthy
energy drink or Fitness drink last one
for the sparkling is the watermelon I
saved it for last because who doesn't
like watermelon it's got to be
good H actually I really don't like it
you don't hear me say that too much in
my videos I mean unless you watch me
drink the 5H Hour Energy that stuff
tastes disgusting but it works as for
this I'm not sure if it's cuz I had the
other three flavors and they were a
little bit stronger so I'm going to give
it a minute and then try it out again
all right let's try it again
nope still don't like it um it doesn't
taste like watermelon to me I get a hint
of aftertaste of melon but what's
hitting me is that sparkling flavor that
I don't like it seems to be a little
more pronounced in this drink maybe
because watermelon is usually a lighter
flavor and they were trying to keep it
not that sweet like the other drinks as
well I think it needs to be a little bit
sweeter to help overpower that sparkling
Flavor now if I'm going to be unbiased
and say I'm pushing the sparkling flavor
to the side and just tasting the
watermelon I don't taste much melon in
here so on to the next one next up is
the raspberry assai
non-carbonated H I'm not a huge fan of
this one either for some reason it's not
very sweet and the raspberry flavor is a
little bit low maybe the assai is a
little bit too high because usually when
I have a blueberry acai I can usually
taste more blueberry or anything with
asai I can usually taste the other
flavor more than the assai but if you
like the flavor of assai you're going to
have a little bit more acai in here than
your raspberry also if I didn't say it
it's not really that sweet so I tend to
pick up one of the other ones for a
little bit more sucrose for a little
more sweetness if you don't like sweet
you may like this one and the last one
on the list is the peach mango
non-carbonated come on Celsius let's
finish strong
all right all right they redeem
themselves with their peach mango this
is pretty good from comparing them to
all the rest I still like the grape the
best which is weird cuz I normally don't
like grape but they did a great job with
it this peach mango is probably my
second favorite out of all six of them
it's got a decent Peach flavor a decent
mango flavor not to sound biased
everyone knows that I like peach mango
the best out of most of the energy
drinks I usually tend to gravitate
towards the peach mango so I am
gravitating towards this peach mango as
well but the sweetness isn't too much
but it's got just the right amount of
sweetness
and it balances off that peach and mango
flavor the fact that it's non-carbonated
also makes me a fan of it another plus
to these drinks was that I was able to
find them in the store sometimes when it
comes to these healthy energy drinks you
can't always find them in the store they
actually sell these at Shaws 7-Eleven
and Seasons That's the convenience store
attached to the Big Shell stations so
having a healthy energy drink that's
readily available is always a plus if
you can't find these in a store near you
I'll include a link down below so that
you can find them at Amazon to have them
Shi to your house directly so there you
have it those are the six flavors that I
have a little bit Hit or Miss but I'm
sure you're going to be able to find
something that you like and because
they're so healthy I say try out one
until you find one that you like I know
I'm going to be adding some of those to
my regular mix also makes me wonder if I
should try the Celsius heat faster too
so many reviews so little time thanks
for joining me and until next time have
a great
day or
night by us scientific by us scientific
research studies by us us accredited
scientific research facilities by us
accredited research facil by us
accredited scientific
res by us accredited scientific resource
facilities not resource research by us
accredited scientific research
facilities yes hit the Subscribe button
oh I always forget where it
is for